Welcome again to listen to Folkstories radio show.
Your host again is Risto Vaasranta.
All common folk can send your own poems to our show. I, Risto, will read them out to you in the quiet night.
And as always, what makes this really interesting is that I will be reading them for the first time too.
Let's see the first poem. Sender Markus from Tuosjärvi.
Name of the poem; Missing your embrace.
Is there life in embrace?
Is there death after life?
Is there death in embrace?
More than life's grace.
Can I leave in your company?
Will you give me what is mine?
Embrace me, embrace me.
With love, give me life.
Thank you, Markus.
This was great poetics.
Let's see the next poem. Sender; Jyrki from Kuosjärvi.
Name of the poem; Secret.
Who gives, who takes?
Who brings? Who takes?
Who gives to all?
Who's? Who?
Are they the one who is enough for you?
Or do you have a secret?
Next poem.
Sender, Aulis from Vatasmaa.
Name of the poem: I can't take it anymore.
Life's bread I carry in my clutches.
Food I produce, for whom? Not for myself, for others, continously.
Continously I feed food into mouth. I can't take this anymore, or can I?
Give me. Give me a lot more than I deserve.
Give me bread to my mouth.
Othewise I can't take this anymore.
And, next poem is sent by Juhani from Vuoksjoki.
Name of the poem, Alert Fullness.
We sit quiet, quietly sneaking, quietly sneaking we sit much.
With lots we give. With lots we bring. Lots for us. What will you give me?
There are flowers, there is peace, there is steel, there is power.
Is. Is. Is. That will not change, even if I said otherwise.
It will not change.
That is the truth.
Salute.
And to the next poem that was sent to us by Esa from Viehtimäki.
Name of the poem, From flower to flower.
A bee takes what others bring.
In the morning they drink. In the night they stay awake.
At dusk they worship each other.
How much I like this. How much I like everything.
How much, I don't know. But for us money brings us happiness.
And the next poem comes from Jouko from Lapeenvesi.
Name of the poem, A pump will do.
Second beat, air filling.
With power I strike, for the best of nothing, for the best of me.
I save if I don't use too much force. I save when I use enough force.
With four wheels, with two wheels. Does it matter in the end which I use?
I pump, so I look good.
And the next poem is from Veikko who didn't tell where he lives.
Name of the poem, Small hand.
Small hand's touch. Big hand's wish.
Will you sit in my lap? Will you too sit in my lap?
Which one of you wants more?
Can you forgive me? Forgive me with love?
Can you do this for me?
I will listen to you. I will take from you what you give me.
I won't give. I won't take. I just live. Is that wrong?
And the next poem, the last of the evening. Is from an anonymous person.
Name of the poem, Greetings.
Risto please go fu--- Uhuh, oops.
That's all for folk poems for now. Tune back later and veeryy goood niiight.