Welcome again to follow folk poem's radio show. I Risto Vaasranta will be your host.
You can all send your poems to the show. I will read them in the night's quiet grace.
And as always, what makes this interesting is that I will be reading them for the first time.
Let's take the first poem of the night. This one was sent by Matti from Maankorpi.
Name of the poem, People's dues.
Companies reap what they sow. The people want much more.
Does my life have dues? Does my life have a meaning?
From account to account, money, always just money.
From account to another. I eat my money every day.
And the next poem comes from Veikko in Niuva.
Name of the poem, Gentle touch.
When you look at me, what do you see? Will you touch me like I touch you?
Will you touch me like I touch you? Will this end? Will this not end? How can I serve better?
Humanity's hope, is it my responsibility? Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
I miss small and warm in my lap. I miss two small and warm in my lap.
I won't put them in a barrel. I will just hold them in my lap.
And the next poem is from Reima in Lappeenpohja.
Name of the poem, Lottery.
If I got a million, I would marry the world, I would get married, if I had time for it.
A woman will do, whoever woman, I won't choose wrong, I will choose the best for me.
Oh, let me win in the lottery, let me win the lottery of love.
My life would be worth millions if I could embrace you, Irma.
Do you hear me? I cry.
And the next poem is from Arvi in Pohjanpolska.
Name of the poem, To you, to me, to everyone else.
Do I sit in the spring, in autumn worshiping, your breast, crying?
From my lap I wrap a pretty phrase, a song phrase, a phrase of a song.
To the ground I sow a potato.
From potato I make soup. From the soup, a tune of love.
My phrase is, sausage soup, a'la carte.
And the next poem is from Teppo in Laitesmaa.
Name of the poem, Reindeer.
I go a long way, to the other side of the world.
There I see life, experience life, how I need you, how you need me, how you need us.
Be my reindeer.
Be for me, what jumps afar, be my Christmas.
And the next poem is from Kaapo in Enteisto.
Name of the poem, Box of confectionery.
I close you in my heart, I close you all the time. Who has the last bite?
Will it fit in your mouth like it does in mine?
Or will it fit in someone else's mouth?
What might be the contents? Will it be sweet or will it be sour?
I can't understand. Who can resist these? Best taste. Be my confectionery.
Next poem is from Juhani in Paasjarvi.
Name of the poem, Life's milk.
I hope much from life. From the store I get my milk. I feel proud, at the cashier.
When we don't have anything to give, anyone else but ourselves.
Do we value whom makes milk for us?
Do we value whom makes us drink it?
Do we value anyone? Anyone who really needs it?
Give us value, be my mercy.
And the last poem of the night, sent to us by anonymous.
Name of the poem, Truth.
Who's bread will you eat, when nights are dark for all.
Much you speak, do little. Who believes this?
Again, again and again. The nights are spoiled again.
Has anyone ever needed poems?
Risto go fuc--- Right...
Yeah...