Seppo Kävyntähkä here from Nature Calls, nature show.
I am now in real wilderness in Lapland. Location Riuhkonperä.
I am looking around the nature. The nature is beautiful today, in my opinion at least.
It's always very proud looking.
Especially this Lapland's nature... creates miracles in the human heart.
There are all sorts of birds and animals here, such as
Scortchy and S-sh-shorewoodpecker
Also, one bird is, Lazyryebird and Crewpa.
Crewpa can be spotted from it's, uh, shady guttural voice when he, uh, uses mating ritual calls to get females.
The noise is more or less like...
In the mountains live... animals such as...
Bannercranker and...
Common awninger
Both are birds.
And for the big game, I could mention ones like...
Speebo...
And Snotish.
Small game worth mentioning is...
S-s-si... Uh...
Rayback.
And, uh, Scritchy.
And... birds... Around... I see... Many...
Critters such as...
Rye... Rye... Ryegroundtit.
And...
Teisko
Teisko eats, most commonly, small food, that you can find on the ground.
It is... for example...
For example, a small animal like....
Tu... Ta... Tari
And... Sea creatures, should mention, fish, here in the forest... Uh... Like...
Like, Wayne. And...
And... S-s-sparkely.
And... I should mention about the big game, that move around here... All the time... On all fours.
Aaaand... When I get close they run on two feet.
They run away at that point, I recommend everyone to do the same.
But for example, an animal such as...
Ha-har-ha.... Boardyboard.
It brings with it...
Uh... If you see one then...
Him, uh, one of them brings many boardyboars with it and they eat all the bits, that are left over from a person.
Let's take one...
One of the nature's, single, uh, birds.
The, uh, these...
These birds such as...
Cloud and uh... Pove.
These birds are... very greedy... in nature, I've lived...
Very long, in my life. Contradictory to what people say.
I haven't...
Umm... Jukka!
Jukka!
How long do I have to do this?
JUKKA!
I'm getting cold!
Well... Cold!
Come here yourself! To do this!
I'm running out of names.
Jukka!
Predatory birds in Lapland's nature are... The one of one is...
Laddle.
The other one is...
Root... jackdaw.
And uhh... Panickytit
Is one... class.
That came to mind...
And... ummm...
Then there is, birds, I should mention is Testicle snatcher.
They do all sorts of... Pranks...
To other organisms animals, in nature.
And, at the sea I can see...
Putviainen with a friend, Teukka.
Jukka!
Perkele, he left already...
No, he's going over there. God help me.
Well, let's look around for a while here, what's on the ground.
On the ground is...
Scumbaggery and...
S-s-snek.
And...
Let's take another, uh, let's see...
Ha-ha-hall... Accounting.
Here...
Birds, if we list some, is, Canopy ash woodcock.
Both have wings, and are flying, in the sky.
Sometimes near the ground, maybe.
In the wind, like you maybe able to hear.
It's windy here.
What is it...
What else is there in nature? There is...
Rir-rir-riranglerod and Track flycatcher.
Let's take... Sometime again...
Transmission ends here.
Thank you all, Nature Calls show listeners. The first episode was here.
If another episode comes out sometime, then...
Call somebody... They will probably come and do it.
I'm going to leave now.