This noise didn't certainly come from a food bell, instead now starts Marko Kahjo's storytime.
I'm sorry for anyone hungry, who mistook it as a food bell.
Wise Dog.
Once upon a time there was a dog who according to their owners was very wise.
If you commanded to sit the dog would sit, to make it's owners happy, and to receive a treat.
And if you asked for a paw, the dog knew to give it.
Again the hound would get a piece of sausage.
It would even go lie on the ground on command.
Well isn't that a smart dog, everyone wondered and was SO proud.
But, give the dog a paper full of algebraic hyperbole functions and tell it to simplify. I'm willing to bet that the dog can't do this.
No. No matter how much sausage was on display.
Well, isn't that a supposedly smart dog, can't even do hyperbole functions.
I can't do them either, but I'm not a dog.
Security Eating
Hunger is forever. Sometimes you don't feel it but you always carry it with you.
As it one in a while pops up, out of nowhere, even though you were sure the last time it went away it would stay away.
But no, you can't get rid of hunger forever. It waits for the opportune time to attack!
And when you get hungry, you need to eat.
Sometimes, even though you're not hungry, you anticipate the future hunger.
When you know that the hunger is coming, you move it even further into the future.
This is called Security Eating.
It is good to eat, in case you're going on a long trip, into storage.
Your body can then consume for it's own needs, that meat pie with two wieners.
A full stomach is much better than an empty one or a flatulent one in case you're lactose intolerant and accidently consume dairy products.
Security Eating can turn against itself.
Badly timed security eating, right before well timed lunch break, can make you unable to eat during the time alloted for food.
This in turn causes the stored energy to be consumed considerably sooner than the next time you can eat.
So, be careful with the timing. Weren't you already taught as a child not to eat candy before lunch so you don't lose your appetite?
But did you learn? No!
Fatso.
My friend is beautiful.
The seagul that flies to the ship.
High in the clouds.
White are the wings like in the mail.
This heavy mail I have to transport.
Seagull's beautiful flight.
Flight so delicate.
Infinite path is a long path to fly.
The flying seagull is white.
Like my thoughts, are white.
Snow's cleanliness is delicatehehghegh so beautiful, so sensitive, so pristine.
Nothing can soil it, not in this naturehheehgh.
Nature that is in itself pristine.
Small bird's.
Small bird's~~
And wax(?)
Small birds they fly.
Out of my hands, out of yours.
A world where factory smokestacks rise up into the heavens.
Black, brown, blankets the earth.
A human being can't breath in it.
It is so black, the mind and the sky, this.
Now I raise my eyes to the horizon.
There fields, there forests, there fjeld rivers.
Oh, my, travel short over there. <i>Is it clear who's gonna pay me?</i> It is so long that I couldn't<i>Hey! Who's gonna pay me? Okay.</i>
Free dream is here like be like nature.
I need to get up, fly into the sky.
Like a seagull, with white wings.
That carries my thoughts into youngster views.
There that beautiful light, that shines like a fjeld. Calls me there, calls people there.
Oh, alone could, go, oh, alone, could go.
Oh I wish I could alone go there.
That was nothing.
Uninvited Guests.
Scabies is one nasty little bugger.
You know, those tiny, practically microscopic, critters females of burrow into your skin and lay eggs inside.
And they don't even ask for permission.
It is part of good manners to let you know if they're going to eat into the area between your fingers, or wrists, or knees, or penis.
Especially annoying is that they may live in between your fingers, or on the wrist, or knee, or penis mane weeks before they notify you with a nasty itch that hey,
"I laid a couple dozen eggs into you two weeks ago and now we're having a party here so, jealous?"
Not at all. I find it fun to get to know new persons.
And the bastards don't even pay taxes and make babies in secret.
I doubt they'll even be accepted anywhere since they act like gypsies and give birth wherever.
Luckily modern medicine has progressed far enough that you can get an ointment from the pharmacy.
Yippee, now stops the itching!
But what does the instructions say?
Itching may continue two to three weeks after treatment. Side effects, redness, rash, eczema.
Depressing text. It sounds worse than the scabies itself.
Why doesn't it say this:
There is no treatment to scabies, they come, lay eggs and only die when their host does.
If the itching in between your fingers, on your wrist, on knees, or in the penis starts to become overbearing.
As a treatment you can chop the mentioned appendage off.
Side effects: bleeding, pain, loss of the mentioned appendix.
If the treatment doesn't work in three weeks you're already dead and maggots are eating you from the inside out in your grave.
Females are nothing but trouble.