At 5:50 a weather report for seafarers.
Strong wind warning.
Kvarken and Bothnian Bay southern wind tomorrow 16 meters per second.
Bothnian Sea southern and southwestern wind tomorrow 14 meters per second.
Expected until tomorrow evening
Gulf of Finland, northern Baltic Sea, Sea of Åland, Archipelago Sea, southern and southwestern winds 8 to 12 meters per second.
Mostly good visibility.
South Bothnian Sea, southern and southewestern winds 8 to 12 meters per second.
Wind speed increases during the day. In the evening 10 to 14 meters per second.
Mostly good visibility.
Spotty rain during night.
Kvarken and Northern Bothian Sea increasing wind speeds. During small hours 10 to 14 meters per second.
Wind speed increases during the day. In the evening 12 to 16 meters per second.
Spotty fog, raining sleet during the night.
Saimaa, southern winds 2 to 6 meters per second.
Starting from morning 4 to 7 meters per second.
Spotty nutu(wtf is nutu?)
Next two days for seafarers.
Expected from Tuesday to Wednesday Gulf of Finland, northern Baltic Sea, Sea of Åland, Archipelago Sea.
Southern to western winds harsh wind probability 70%. In the evening western and northern wind less than 14 meters per second.
Gulf of Bothnia, during the night southern and western winds less than 14 meters per seconds. In the evening western and northern winds. Probability of harsh winds 40%.