Welcome again to wish cassette show.
You can still send us cassettes to play.
You can leave them to our Alivieska's office, where the newspaper ads and such are left too.
You can bring them there and please leave a note with them, especially if the cassette doesn't say anything.
Without further ado, let's put the first one playing,
It says, Duck pond's guns glaze patch song.
I will tell you about glazing. There are many types of glazes. There are thousands of resources.
Is manganese, and sulfates, and copper oxides, you can use almost anything for glazing.
Your imagination is the limit, even if that.
But I don't want to go do laboratory glazing tests for three hours tomorrow because I might get calcium dust into my lungs, that's not good.
Glazing has it's own hazards. Making glazing takes spirit. I can't motivate myself. No way, No!
No! No I can't!
No I can't!
That was, quite a nice song, I didn't really get the lyrics though, what they were trying to say,
I can't say.
It wasn't bad. Let's take the next song right away.
Right, I could say here, that we wish the songs you send would be short.
We don't want any six or seven minute long, not even five minute, short like three minutes so we can play many during the show.
This was good in that, that it was short.
Let's take the next one, this cassette is in bad condition.
Here, what happened to this cassette? It has paint on it and different color paints sprayed on it and the paper has ripped a little too.
The paper reads with bad writing. Why does stuff break? I don't know if that's the name of the song but let's play it.
Why shit breaks?
Take a new microphone, the old breaks!
The old breaks! ... Perkele ... microphone ... God help me ... doesn't work ... go fuck yourself ... saatana hell ...
Damnit, these kinds you shouldn't send here at all, this isn't music at all
it's just some ruckus and banging and just shouting.
Nobody healthy listens to this.
Completely deranged this stuff, whoever made this, go to a doctor, there's something really wrong with you.
Goodness... The world has turned into a weird place since people are doing stuff like that.
I won't say any more about it, otherwise I'll say some bad words.
I'll let it go, but don't send stuff like this here, that was worthless.
Yeah, maybe the next one is better. This one reads, Sauna sausage. Let's put that one on.
Loylya, inside sits sweaty.
Hot, moist slips into mouth. Salty, tasty, snaps under the teeth.
A cheesy weiner slips into a mouth.
Sauna sausage
On lips, sweaty and moist.
Oven, hisses, sausage does the same,
Bottle cork hisses, dude rejoices.
More steam, wash our backs together.
Then sausage slips, in between the cheeks it flips.
Sauna sausage
On the lips sweaty and moist.
Sauna sausage good, is.
Well, that one was, a jovial song, nothing bad to say about this. This was real music and not just wanking and mindless stuff.
This was really fun and it made me happy, and I kinda want to have a sausage now.
Now that the ad break is coming soon, maybe I'll go to the nearby store and get me some sausage.
Yeah, now we'll go on an ad break and we'll continue sometime later.