And, welcome to Alivieska orienteering carnival.
With you today, Alivieska radio's Antti Kananen.
Orienteering carnivals are held now for the 16th time.
And this year, every day, on this week, we get to follow, this great sport event.
Competitor count has been for the past few years going down.
On orienteering's part that's a normal occurence all around Finland.
As the popularity of orienteering goes down.
As floorball and other sports gain more popularity.
But still, orienteering carnival on their own part try to keep up with this magnificent sport's traditions.
In men's class, there are over 400 competitors this year.
I could mention a few of the more interesting ones from the starting list.
Reima Rehvonmäki, has already left, he was among the first ones.
He is an experienced competitor. For many years he has belonged to the carnival's competitors.
He hasn't won once yet though.
Best he has gotten was bronze from 8 years ago.
But Reima is in good health and is part of the medal candidates, to say the least.
Matti Ahvenainen, is with us again.
Jari Mäennummi, remember his name when the