I've got this rock & roll, in my spirit plays rock & roll and rock & roll is everything.
I was bullied in school, the laestadianists didn't believe in ölvis. (note: I've no clue what this means)
The teachers did nothing, they said Jesus goes all the way.
I've got this rock & roll, in my spirit plays rock & roll and rock & roll is everything.
I went to civilian service, didn't fit into the army.
In formation I yelled, Hey! Rock & roll is here to stay!
From service to a job, didn't get a good job.
Didnt' bother, I said yes, pow, holy.
I met a pretty girl, or well, a girl at least.
I didn't catch anything, anything incurable at least.
On the third date, two lines on the birth test.
We married, even though my father in law told me to---
I've got this rock & roll, in my spirit plays rock & roll and rock & roll is everything.