It was my 12th birthday.
My dad burnt my wooden toy train.
We dumped the ashes, there was no time for tears. My dad told me to take it like a man.
Even though my roots don't reach to the bottom. They stick to this frozen land.
Nobody tells me what to do. I will find my own way.
My brother came back from the army, he made corporal.
The bar was too low, didn't make it to sergeant, dad's a sergeant.
Mom doesn't have the strength.
Sometimes she's quiet for weeks.
The doctors say, she's doing it on purpose.
Aunt brought her to the hospital.
Even though my roots don't reach to the bottom. They stick to this frozen land.
Nobody tells me what to do. I will find my own way.
Even though my roots don't reach to the bottom.
Even though my roots don't reach to the bottom. They stick to this frozen land.
Nobody tells me what to do. I will find my own way.