The summer was like a hot cow's breath.
To wash it off we rode our bikes.
Too small muddy shore.
We cursed only the factory's smell.
Last on top of youth association's hill was the loser.
And from those days there's only pieces left, but we take from them something better to adulthood.
The skateboard had a blue dragon on the bottom, ordered from all the way from America.
Tennis field had one empty spot, with one jump the whole summer was over.
We hid our beer next to the tracks in the forest, and greeted the train with our bare asses.
Before the city, ten in bag and a marlboro pack. Someone from college got the best girl.
Don't loose the game, remember to smile at the girls.
And from those days there's only pieces left, but we take from them something better to adulthood.
Someone was stronger than me at a bus stop, it's easy if you have a friend.
Running through the forest the branches whacked my face, but it hurt more to be a coward.
And when we got older we paid it all back with interest.
And from those days there's only pieces left, but we take from them something better to adulthood.