Shit in pants. Roaming. To the breadline. Slouching.
My mind keeps wandering. Soon my thirst is quenching!
Yeahaha.
Hey don't, backup, I've got to shit.
Shit in my pants. Where did he go? Don't try to pick me up you'll lift shit instead.
Shit in pants. Roaming. To the breadline. Slouching.
My mind keeps wandering. Soon my thirst is quenching!
Pena, give me a drink.
Take from this. Let's go to the pub and pick up stumps from the ground and see who has more shit in pants.
Oh, this is good.
Yes!
Shit in pants. Roaming. To the breadline. Slouching.
My mind keeps wandering. Soon my thirst is quenching!
A moment more and I'm sipping! A moment more and I'm sipping! A moment more!
Sipping!