I was thinking about the last thing...
I've also played video games too sometime, or well...
Not a lot recently but I have to admit that there are good games available, you just need to play them with moderation.
Going back memory lane, -89 when my cousin was working in book pressing at Alavuo.
They needed some people to work there. I spent what, three weeks there?
So we there during work we played as they had brought this thing, some company was pushing digitalization to them or something.
The technology was going digital.
But, all we did with the computer was play Larry.
That was a good game, we played it with my cousin when we had some leftover time from work.
It was such a sweet game.
It was a bit, uh, how'd I put this, made for adults,
when you got further in the game you got into some love making, but as this is a family show I won't go into details here.
There was all sorts of other stuff too, drove around with a taxi, went to a casino to play, stuff like that.
It was good that my cousin knows English a little better than I do so we got pretty far in the game but,
Damn it, we had a bit over a week left of work, but that damn guy came and took the computer away.
So we didn't play it through, but I have to say that Larry is a good game.