Good evening everyone from Alivieska's local radio.
And today we're hearing things through the grapevine.
You can call us here in the studio. The number is the old 241152.
We have our first caller on the lines.
Repa from the grapevine, who's there?
It's me again here!
Who?
Anssi!
Anssi Ranssila!
You should remember, we were at Ilottila at the same time.
Hmm... Pertti's son?
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah, I mean. I called because, I heard from the pub that you're no longer with Sirpa?
I thought asking her out for a coffee. See my woman left, so I dont... Nobody has washed my clothes in two months.
So I thought I'll call Sirpa, so if she would go for a beer and then unf unf.
So would you give me her number?
I'm not going to start spewing out my personal life on the radio.
What?! Gimme gimme!
I'm not giving you anything. This is a completely inappropriate place to ask for that.
Oh pussy! You've always been a pisshead like that! Oh pussy what a guy!
Pussy! I'm coming over to kill you!
Oh pussy! Sirpa! Call me if you hear this! Quickly!
I'm going to come there and saatana--
For all the listeners, know that we don't want calls like this here.
Leave personal matters elsewhere, call amongst your friends, and talk in the pub but don't bring them here in the radio.
Well, alright. We have another caller on the line. Who is it?
Yeah, It's Markku Joroma here, I wanted to call about the town hall.
It's nothing weird, but why the saatana did you have to paint it with such a bright color?
It's decadent and vulgar.
A queer job, it's all for fags or something.
It doesn't belong here in Alivieska at all.
This could a question of taste too, right?
Yes, but it's a different matter since this is about the town hall.
It represents, like, this our, county and our society so it can't be like that.
The buildings nearby are pretty same color so could that have affected it?
Yeah yeah, but it's a completely different matter if it's a personal home. That can be painted pick and it's going out of their own pocket but
town hall can't be red like that. It has to be gray.
But that's all from me.
A message to the heads in the town hall, saatana's blubber brains, paint it gray.
Like it used to be. Yeah, goodbye.
Let's take the next caller immediately since there seems to be someone on the lines already.
It's Anssi here.
I'm not going come come punch you yet, if you put the Jorma Pulkkone's Riitta Rakas playing.
Yeah and the phone number you can go drop in my mailbox for tomorrow.
I'll come if it's not there!
I'm getting pretty fed up with the grapevines for now so... How about I'll just put the
Jorma Pulkkonen and co playing as so many have requested it.
And we'll continue after that with something else.