We drink beer, chat and listen to the radio.
Alivieska's local radio 91Mhz. From baby to grandpa, suits all.
Welcome again to the grapevines. Let's talk about things again.
You can call us again, the number is the same old, 241152.
Don't forget to add the Northern Pohjanmaa area code, if you want to call.
Who is it?
Masa here, I was listening to your advert and they sing so far off key that my ears are bleeding now so what's up with this?
The advert was sung by Alivieska's war veterans. So did you have something to say about their singing capability?
Oh, war veterans? Never mind then.
Let's take the next caller. Who's there?
Well it's Kosola's grandma, hello.
Hello, hello.
I wanted to call and tell you that I'm afraid.
What are you afraid of?
The noises.
What noises?
The noises that I hear.
Where do these noises come from?
It's those, youngsters are driving around with their mopeds in the town all the time.
Aha...
They make such loud noises when they drive around and rev their mopeds.
I don't dare go buy even coffee from the kiosk, because there's a large group of people there, it's wild, completely wild.
Have you said anything to them about this?
Couldn't you just ban the mopeds from downtown, and elsewhere too?
No you can't ban them, in a free society, if they're not doing anything wrong.
I remember when I was young with Terttu.
When the first Pappatunturi mopeds came out, yuk, we didn't even look at those guys.
It's such a thing that the young people will grow up rotten, all of them.
Girls become whores and boys become scoundrels.
You could ban the mopeds altogether so-
I doubt that will ever happen. There's no way Finnish law would allow something like that.
The municipality leaders can't just overthrow law just like that.
This won't do at all. Not at all.
So you haven't tried talking to them?
No, it's every night, every night. Many times during the day, probably don't even go to school.
Complete brats the whole lot. That's how it is.
I'd like to send greetings to Terttu, and Aili, and also, Kerttu, and, Raili.
And, if Isko hears this, greetings to Isko.
You will probably be at the wheat table drinking lots of coffee. (wheat table, old-timer slang for serving table)
And, of course, Raimo.
And now that Christmas is so close I could sing a little Christmas tune here.
I think we got some kind of a technical fault here. The connection just cut off suddenly. Bummer.
I think that was the essentials, let's take our next caller. Who's there?
Jorma Marppo here, we discussed with our hunting party at a laavu.
I heard that hunting elk or moose or whatever is illegal with a rocket launcher or flamethrower is illegal.
Saatana, they decided this in Brussels, now that Finland is in the EU.
God damnit, they can't just tell us what to do.
So you were going to hunt with a flamethrower and a rocket launcher?
No, I don't mean that I would do something like that, I like to eat the meat, see.
It's no use if the animal is charred or in a thousand little pieces but,
it should still be allowed, in case someone wants to hunt like it. Whatever floats your boat.
Isn't it a little extreme hunting with that kind of equipment?
I wouldn't say it's extreme, or well it's just as extreme as our culture here in Finland.
Nobody in Brussels can't say what we can do here.
If we want to hunt like this, it's god damnit just like we want to do it.
If some Brussels' sir wants to ban this then damn it we'll blow up the whole Brussels.
We talked and decided that if this is how it's going to go we'll march there and blow the whole place up.
I have nothing else to say. I've said enough for them to think about. Bye.
What is there to add to that?
Grapevines are here. Next up, some music. I'm going to get coffee.